This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Rogers, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
Thanks to a final charge from Whitebeard's associates,
success seemed to be within Luffy's grasp.
But then, the unthinkable happened,
and Admiral Aka'inu landed a fatal blow against Luffy's brother.
Pops.
I didn't see it,
I think,
my family...
and you,
Luffy...
Thank you...
for caring about someone like me,
who is good for nothing
who this world never wanted.
Luffy has such bad blood in his veins.
blood in his veins.
Thank you...
for loving me.
The Navy Headquarters Falls! Whitebeard's unspeakable wrath!
Ace...
Scarlet out?
Scarlet out...
You didn't really think I was dead, did you?
Yeah, well I'm not!
So stop your crying and have some faith for once!
I promise, I'm not gonna die, okay?
Not ever.
At least not as long as I've got a wussy little brother who needs me to protect him.
Darp, please look after my child.
Our son's name is Goldie Ace.
It's the truth.
All it takes to become brothers is to share some sake.
All right, from here on out, we're honest to goodness brothers.
But we were so close!
Aze!
I...
No, mate!
Oh, my...
Please!
They got Firefist!
He's dead!
Strawboy, no!
The poor kid's shutting down!
He's gonna get killed!
Akeinu!
I won't miss twice!
There's no one to save you!
It's over, Straw Hats!
I've seen enough death for today!
Back off!
Wake up! Luffy!
We have to run!
Move or you're next!
Listen! We cannot give in to despair!
Go! Carry Straw Hat if he won't run! Hurry!
We may have lost Ace today, but he'll live on through Luffy!
You're right, boss.
Just...
If Ace can't protect him, then as his family, we have to step up!
Ace is our brother!
Fight like your pride's on the line!
In his honor!
Pull it together for your brother's sake, Luffy!
When I hold an execution, I make damn sure to finish the job!
You can't run from me!
Look behind you!
We would be lonely!
I'm alsooterial dark, but not 15 minutes!
When guys take up on me with the nail, my patience
Pig.
I'm turning in turn into less!
Princess regards quick with him!
In the backkle, there's no room to rest!
How we're gonna stop you doing!
wno onder that alleen exceptional pig!
Let's do this!
We've just wanted to relax who gets you now!
Let's go!
Might as well here!
We can respond to theelyn six soldiers!
Damn, he's mad as hell!
Come on, we gotta get out of here!
Look out!
Will home!
Oh, no!
Time for you to step down.
Pops!
Damn it!
You okay?
No!
Hey, Pops.
What's wrong?
It's not over yet.
Don't give up, Pops!
We can't lose you!
Stand up!
Huuuhh!
Aaaaaahhhh!
He's coming!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
C's protection!
Logan and I have såd market!
T-fight!
No!
For the more than just this, they will buy
C trip kişily Race
Folge 2
Strike Source
ARUNME
ony
expire
Gunt
Now
Mary
Girls
Well
I'll help you
we'll lose
Karma
Two
Many
Princess
жизнь
Charge
No
He's too strong!
HQ's done for!
Son of a...
Whitefeel!
Admiral Sakazuki!
Come on, help!
Help!
Come on!
I... I think it's stopped.
Is he okay?
Dammit, why?!
The closet split in half!
We can't reach the pirates!
Awaiting orders!
He's stuck over there!
We can't even fight!
But why?!
Don't leave us!
Please!
I thought the man was on his last leg.
Where is all this power coming from?!
Want more?
I am your enemy!
And I alone!
So if you have a resolve to face me...
Come!
I am your enemy!
And I alone!
So if you have a resolve to face me...
Come!
That was good!
I got scared!
Let's go!
Retreat! Get back to the ship!
Hell no!
All we can do is honor his wishes.
As his sons, we should be grateful and hold our heads up high.
Save your tears for later. Let's move!
I'm done. I can't.
Stand up!
If a ship can sail, bring it to the bayhead and line him off!
He can still shoot you, dammit!
Stop wasting time!
Salome, take me to Luffy. I fear for his safety.
Sorry for disobeying orders, but someone's got to watch this to the end, Pops.
Please.
Ahh!
Grr!
Aah!
Ooh!
Ahh!
Hey, look!
What the hell is that?
It's huge!
Whatever it is, it can't be good!
Oops, they found me.
There's someone else, too!
There's a whole group of people up on the scaffold!
You fellas ain't very observant, are you?
Blackbeard, it seems you've made some new friends.
I thought they were locked up and impelled down!
Teach!
They were supposed to be erased from history!
After the crimes they committed, even death was too great a mercy!
He's the largest living creature in the world!
The great battleship, San Juan Wolf!
Wow, they even know my name.
Well, I'll be...
The corrupt king, Pablo Pizarro!
Meow, I'm back!
Meow, you die!
Heavy drinker, Vasco, shut!
I'm gonna go ahead and kill them all, okay?
Crescent Moon Hunter, Katarina Devon!
Maroon!
You boys want this?
Try me!
And that's the old jail manager from Impel Down!
Shiryu of the Reign!
They've joined the Blackbeard Pirates!
Fi...
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Hey there, pups!
I'm glad I could make it to your funeral!
You miss me?
You fat bastard!
Blackbeard appears, his murder of Thatch and his capture of Ace, all part of a terrifying
plan that no one could have imagined.
With the war at Marineford in its final stage, Whitebeard fights to avenge his fallen sons
and punish the traitor who has plotted his undoing.
On the next, One Piece, ending the matter.
Whitebeard versus the Blackbeard pirates, I'm going to be king of the pirates!